Konvitz, Milton R. Papers /4039
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Series II: Subject FIles, 1942-1986
  - Negro in Medicine. (Box 135, Folder 14)
  - Negro Organizers. (Box 135, Folder 15)
  - Negro: What He Wants., 1960 (Box 135, Folder 16)
    8/30/60 unpublished manuscript "What the Negro Wants: Negro and White Conceptions" by Charles Grigg and Lewis Miller.
  - Nelson. (Box 135, Folder 17)
  - NEMA. (Box 135, Folder 18)
  - Neo-Nazism. (Box 135, Folder 19)
  - New Deal. (Box 135, Folder 20)
  - New Economic Library. (Box 135, Folder 21)
  - New Jersey. (Box 135, Folder 22)
  - New Jersey Department of Education: Division Against Discrimination. (Box 135, Folder 23)
  - New Jersey Federal Employment Practices Commission. (Box 135, Folder 24)
  - New Jersey Public Utility Law. (Box 135, Folder 25)
  - New Jersey Supreme Court. (Box 135, Folder 26)
  - New Jersey Telephone Case. (Box 135, Folder 27)
  - New Leader. (Box 135, Folder 28)
  - New Left. (Box 136, Folder 1)
  - New Legislation. (Box 136, Folder 2)
  - New Mexico. (Box 136, Folder 3)
  - New Party. (Box 136, Folder 4)
  - New Right. (Box 136, Folder 5)
  - New School. (Box 136, Folder 6)
  - New York City. (Box 136, Folder 7)
  - New York City. (Box 136, Folder 8)
  - New York City Division of Labor Relations. (Box 136, Folder 9)
  - New York Civil Liberties Union. (Box 136, Folder 10)
  - New York Committee to Abolish Capital Punishment. (Box 136, Folder 11)
  - New York State. (Box 136, Folder 12)
  - New York State. (Box 136, Folder 13)
  - New York State Commission Against Discrimination. (Box 136, Folder 14)
  - New York State Constitutional Convention., 1967 (Box 136, Folder 15)
  - New York State Labor Law. (Box 136, Folder 16)
  - New York State Labor Relations Board. (Box 136, Folder 17)
  - New York State Labor Relations Board. (Box 137, Folder 1)
  - New York State Retirees Public Employees Federation. (Box 137, Folder 2)
  - New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations (NYSSILR): Alumni., 1963 (Box 137, Folder 3)
    Alumni Survey
  - NYSSILR: Documentation Center., 1954-1956 (Box 137, Folder 4)
  - NYSSILR [folder 1 of 5], 1953-1964 (Box 137, Folder 5)
    Minutes of faculty meetings; 1963 reprint, "The Founding of the New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations: A Tribute to Irving M. Ives and Edmund Ezra Day" by M. R. Konvitz; Reports of the Dean 1953-64; "ILR Alumni Survey", 1956, 1960; "Annu
  - NYSSILR [folder 2 of 5], 1953-1964 (Box 137, Folder 6)
  - NYSSILR [folder 3 of 5], 1953-1964 (Box 137, Folder 7)
  - NYSSILR [folder 4 of 5], 1953-1964 (Box 137, Folder 8)
  - NYSSILR [folder 5 of 5], 1953-1964 (Box 137, Folder 9)
  - New York Times. (Box 137, Folder 10)
  - New York University. (Box 137, Folder 11)
  - Newark. (Box 137, Folder 12)
  - Newbury, Frank D. (Box 137, Folder 13)
  - Newman Club. (Box 137, Folder 14)
  - Newspaper. (Box 137, Folder 15)
  - Newspapers., 1967 (Box 137, Folder 16)
    Letter, with attachment, signed by Senator Philip A. Hart.
  - Newspaper Strike. (Box 137, Folder 17)
  - Niebuhr, Reinhold. (Box 138, Folder 1)
  - Niemoller. (Box 138, Folder 2)
  - Nigeria. (Box 138, Folder 3)
  - Nightwork. (Box 138, Folder 4)
  - Nixon, Richard M. (Box 138, Folder 5)
  - Nixon, Richard M., 1976 (Box 138, Folder 6)
  - Nixon Pardon. (Box 138, Folder 7)
  - Nixon vs. U.S. (Box 138, Folder 8)
  - Noise. (Box 138, Folder 9)
  - No-Strike Provision. (Box 138, Folder 10)
  - Non-Communist Affidavit. (Box 138, Folder 11)
  - Nonconformity. (Box 138, Folder 12)
  - Non-Proliferation Treaty. (Box 138, Folder 13)
  - Non-Violence. (Box 138, Folder 14)
  - North Atlantic Treaty Organization (NATO). (Box 138, Folder 15)
  - Norris-La Guardia Act. (Box 138, Folder 16)
  - Nuclear War. (Box 138, Folder 17)
  - Nudism. (Box 138, Folder 18)
  - Nudity. (Box 138, Folder 19)
  - Nurenburg. (Box 138, Folder 20)
  - Nurses. (Box 138, Folder 21)
  - Oaths. (Box 138, Folder 22)
  - Oaths. (Box 138, Folder 23)
  - Oaths. (Box 138, Folder 24)
  - Obscenity. (Box 138, Folder 25)
  - Obscenity. (Box 138, Folder 26)
  - Obscenity. (Box 138, Folder 27)
  - Obscenity. (Box 138, Folder 28)
  - Obscenity: Bookstores, Movie Houses, etc. (Box 138, Folder 29)
  - Obscenity: Breach of Peace. (Box 138, Folder 30)
  - Obscenity: 1973 Cases. (Box 138, Folder 31)
  - Obscenity: Commission. (Box 139, Folder 1)
  - Obscenity Defined: Ginzberg. (Box 139, Folder 2)
  - Obscenity: Expert Testimony. (Box 139, Folder 3)
  - Obscenity: Foreign. (Box 139, Folder 4)
  - Obscenity: General. (Box 139, Folder 5)
  - Obscenity: Law, Customs, Transportation. (Box 139, Folder 6)
  - Obscenity: New York State Law. (Box 139, Folder 7)
  - Obscenity: Possession, Sale. (Box 139, Folder 8)
  - Obscenity: Press. (Box 139, Folder 9)
  - Obscenity: Privacy. (Box 139, Folder 10)
  - Obscenity: Sale to Minors. (Box 139, Folder 11)
  - Obscenity: Seizure. (Box 139, Folder 12)
  - Ocean Hill: Brownsville. (Box 139, Folder 13)
  - Ocean Hill: Brownsville. (Box 139, Folder 14)
  - Offensive Words. (Box 139, Folder 15)
  - Office of Financial Management. (Box 139, Folder 16)
  - Office of Institutional Projects Abroad. (Box 139, Folder 17)
  - Oil. (Box 139, Folder 18)
  - Oil. (Box 139, Folder 19)
  - Oil, 1976. (Box 139, Folder 20)
  - Oil - World Supply. (Box 139, Folder 21)
  - Old Age. (Box 139, Folder 22)
  - Old Age., 1950 (Box 139, Folder 23)
    3/17/50 progress report to the Federal Security Administrator, "Programs for an Aging Population" by the Working Committee on the Aging.
  - Old Testament. (Box 139, Folder 24)
  - Ombudsman. (Box 139, Folder 25)
  - One World Club. (Box 139, Folder 26)
  - Open Admissions. (Box 139, Folder 27)
  - Open Forum. (Box 139, Folder 28)
  - Opera. (Box 139, Folder 29)
  - Operation Crossroads Africa. (Box 139, Folder 30)
  - Opinion Polls. (Box 139, Folder 31)
  - Opler, Marvin. (Box 139, Folder 32)
  - Oppenheim Case. (Box 139, Folder 33)
  - Opportunity. (Box 139, Folder 34)
  - Optimism. (Box 139, Folder 35)
  - Order of the Coif. (Box 139, Folder 36)
  - ORT. (Box 139, Folder 37)
  - Oxford Center for Post Graduate Hebrew Studies. (Box 139, Folder 38)
  - Oxford University. (Box 139, Folder 39)
  - Pacem in Terris. (Box 140, Folder 1)
  - Pacificism and Labor. (Box 140, Folder 2)
  - Palestine., 1948 (Box 140, Folder 3)
    Rough draft and final article, "Politics and Palestine," by Konvitz, 4 pages.
  - Palestine. (Box 140, Folder 4)
  - Palestine., 1948 (Box 140, Folder 5)
    "Palestine Partition," delivered by Konvitz at a protest rally in the Memorial Room of Willard Straight Hall, 2/25/48.
  - Palestine. (Box 140, Folder 6)
  - Palestine., 1945-1948 (Box 140, Folder 7)
    2 pages, typed paper, dated approximately 1945, no title, on Palestine; typed quotation of Konvitz on Palestine situation, no date; rough draft of Palestine Partition, 2/25/48; 6 typed pages on Palestine, 3/9/48; carbon copy of a letter to the "New York T
  - Palestine., 1948-1949 (Box 140, Folder 8)
    "Inside Israel", Zionist Organization of America, newsletter
  - Palestine Liberation Organization (PLO). (Box 140, Folder 9)
  - Palestinian Question. (Box 140, Folder 10)
  - Palestinians. (Box 140, Folder 11)
  - Palestinians., 1981 (Box 140, Folder 12)
    1/19/81 memo, To: Anti-Defamation League Directors, From: Rabbi Kleniaki, re: Proposed 1981 consideration of U.S. Catholic Conference.
  - Palestinians., 1976 (Box 140, Folder 13)
  - Pan American Association. (Box 140, Folder 14)
  - Parades. (Box 140, Folder 15)
  - Paris. (Box 140, Folder 16)
  - Parks. (Box 140, Folder 17)
  - Parliamentary Procedure. (Box 140, Folder 18)
  - Parochaid. (Box 140, Folder 19)
  - Parochaid., 1976 (Box 141, Folder 1)
  - Parochial. (Box 141, Folder 2)
  - Parochial Schools. (Box 141, Folder 3)
  - Parochial Schools. (Box 141, Folder 4)
  - Party. (Box 141, Folder 5)
  - Party Platforms. (Box 141, Folder 6)
  - Passion Play. (Box 141, Folder 7)
  - Passports. (Box 141, Folder 8)
  - Passports. (Box 141, Folder 9)
  - Passports. (Box 141, Folder 10)
  - Patents. (Box 141, Folder 11)
  - Pattern Bargaining. (Box 141, Folder 12)
  - Patterns of Thought: ILR 69., 1969 (Box 141, Folder 13)
  - Peace Corps. (Box 141, Folder 14)
  - Peace Keeping Ways and Means Committee. (Box 141, Folder 15)
  - Peace Treaties. (Box 141, Folder 16)
  - Peekskill. (Box 141, Folder 17)
  - Peirce Society. (Box 141, Folder 18)
  - Pekarsky, Maurice B. (Box 141, Folder 19)
  - Pekelis. (Box 141, Folder 20)
  - Penal Law. (Box 141, Folder 21)
  - Pension. (Box 141, Folder 22)
  - Pentagon Papers Case. (Box 141, Folder 23)
  - Pentagon Papers. (Box 142, Folder 1)
  - Pentagon Papers. (Box 142, Folder 2)
  - Peonage. (Box 142, Folder 3)
  - People's Lobby., 1949 (Box 142, Folder 4)
    Newsletter, "People's Lobby Bulletin".
  - Perjury. (Box 142, Folder 5)
  - Perkins, Frances. (Box 142, Folder 6)
  - Perkins, James A., 1965 (Box 142, Folder 7)
    Lecture (not for publication), "The University in Transition" by James A. Perkins.
  - Perlman, Mark. (Box 142, Folder 8)
  - Perlman, Selig. (Box 142, Folder 9)
  - Personnel. (Box 142, Folder 10)
  - Petition. (Box 142, Folder 11)
  - Petro Impact, 1982 (Box 142, Folder 12)
  - Phi Alpha Delta. (Box 142, Folder 13)
  - Phi Beta Kappa. (Box 142, Folder 14)
  - Phi Kappa Phi. (Box 142, Folder 15)
  - Philanthropy. (Box 142, Folder 16)
  - Philippines. (Box 142, Folder 17)
  - Philosophy - 1949 r (Box 142, Folder 18)
    Reprint, "Cassirer's Philosophy of Symbolic Forms," signed by Robert S. Hartman.
  - Picketing. (Box 142, Folder 19)
  - Picketing., 1952 (Box 142, Folder 20)
    Reprint, "Picketing-- Free Speech: the Growth of the New Law of Picketing from 1940 to 1952," signed by Joseph Tanenhaus.
  - Picketing., 1919-1938 (Box 142, Folder 21)
    1938 paper, "State Legislation Limiting Labor Injunctions" by National Committee on Labor Injuctions; 1919 paper, "The Debs Decision" by Scott Nearing; 1933 paper, "Spying on Workers" by Robert W. Dunn.
  - Picketing: Historical Philosophy. (Box 142, Folder 22)
  - Picketing: International Protests. (Box 142, Folder 23)
  - Picketing: Labor. (Box 142, Folder 24)
  - Picketing: Labor Law., 1943 (Box 142, Folder 25)
    Memo, by Milton R. Konvitz, re: Work-or-Fight Laws.
  - Picketing: Legal Aspects., 1953 (Box 143, Folder 1)
    Reprint, "Picketing As Free Speech: Early Stages in the Growth of the New Law of Picketing," signed by Joseph Tanenhaus.
  - Picketing: Marsh vs. Alabama. (Box 143, Folder 2)
  - Picketing: 1964 Cases. (Box 143, Folder 3)
  - Picketing: World's Fair 1964. (Box 143, Folder 4)
  - Pi Sigma Alpha. (Box 143, Folder 5)
  - Pike, Bishop James. (Box 143, Folder 6)
  - Pilch, Judah. (Box 143, Folder 7)
  - Planning. (Box 143, Folder 8)
  - Plant Seizure. (Box 143, Folder 9)
  - Plato. (Box 143, Folder 10)
  - Pluralism. (Box 143, Folder 11)
  - Point IV, Foreign Aid. (Box 143, Folder 12)
  - Point IV. (Box 143, Folder 13)
  - Point IV. (Box 143, Folder 14)
  - Point IV. (Box 143, Folder 15)
  - Point IV. (Box 143, Folder 16)
  - Point IV. (Box 143, Folder 17)
  - Point IV. (Box 143, Folder 18)
  - Point IV. (Box 144, Folder 1)
  - Point IV. (Box 144, Folder 2)
  - Poland. (Box 144, Folder 3)
  - Police. (Box 144, Folder 4)
  - Police and Community. (Box 144, Folder 5)
  - Police Power. (Box 144, Folder 6)
  - Political. (Box 144, Folder 7)
  - Political Action. (Box 144, Folder 8)
  - Political Expenditures., 1952 (Box 144, Folder 9)
    Memo, to: Dean Catherwood, from: M. Konvitz, re: Erwin Bill, S. 2646, New York State Senate.
  - Political Parties. (Box 144, Folder 10)
  - Political Rights. (Box 144, Folder 11)
  - Politics. (Box 144, Folder 12)
  - Politics. (Box 144, Folder 13)
  - Poll Tax., 1943 (Box 144, Folder 14)
    Paper, "Why the Poll Tax is a National Issue" by the National Committee to Abolish the Poll Tax.
  - Poll Tax. (Box 144, Folder 15)
  - Poll Tax Repeal. (Box 144, Folder 16)
  - Polls. (Box 144, Folder 17)
  - Population. (Box 144, Folder 18)
  - Population. (Box 144, Folder 19)
  - Pornography. (Box 144, Folder 20)
  - Portal to Portal. (Box 144, Folder 21)
  - Portugal. (Box 144, Folder 22)
  - Post Office. (Box 144, Folder 23)
  - Postmaster General. (Box 144, Folder 24)
  - Pound, Ezra. (Box 145, Folder 1)
  - Pound, Roscoe (Box 145, Folder 2)
  - Poverty. (Box 145, Folder 3)
  - Poverty. (Box 145, Folder 4)
  - Poverty. (Box 145, Folder 5)
  - Poverty. (Box 145, Folder 6)
  - Poverty. (Box 145, Folder 7)
  - Poverty. (Box 145, Folder 8)
  - Poverty. (Box 145, Folder 9)
  - Poverty. (Box 145, Folder 10)
  - Poverty: Anti-Poverty Programs., 1966-1969 (Box 145, Folder 11)
    1968 article, "Lessons We Could Have Learned from the Antipoverty Efforts," signed by Sar A. Levitan.
  - Poverty: Anti-Poverty Programs., 1969-1980 (Box 145, Folder 12)
    1971 letter, with attachment, signed by Representative Charles B. Rangel.
  - Poverty: Aged Persons. (Box 145, Folder 13)
  - Poverty: Area Redevelopment Act. (Box 145, Folder 14)
  - Poverty: Bibliography. (Box 145, Folder 15)
  - Poverty: Budget. (Box 145, Folder 16)
  - Poverty: Business World. (Box 145, Folder 17)
  - Poverty and Civil Liberties. (Box 145, Folder 18)
  - Poverty: Community Action. (Box 145, Folder 19)
  - Poverty: Community Self-Determination Act of 1969. (Box 145, Folder 20)
  - Poverty: Consumer, 1969 (Box 145, Folder 21)
    Letter, with attachment, signed by Representative Benjamin S. Rosenthal of New York.
  - Poverty: Day Care Centers. (Box 146, Folder 1)
  - Poverty: Debt Prison. (Box 146, Folder 2)
  - Poverty: Definition. (Box 146, Folder 3)
  - Poverty: Demonstrations. (Box 146, Folder 4)
  - Poverty: Depressed Areas. (Box 146, Folder 5)
  - Poverty: Economic Opportunity Act. (Box 146, Folder 6)
  - Poverty: Economic Opportunity Report. (Box 146, Folder 7)
  - Poverty: Family. (Box 146, Folder 8)
  - Poverty: Family Allowance Plan. (Box 146, Folder 9)
  - Poverty: Farm. (Box 146, Folder 10)
  - Poverty: In Fiction. (Box 146, Folder 11)
    List of American novels of poems dealing with poverty; list of books on Labor in fiction.
  - Poverty: Food Stamps. (Box 146, Folder 12)
  - Poverty: Guaranteed Annual Wage. (Box 146, Folder 13)
  - Poverty: Hard Core. (Box 146, Folder 14)
  - Poverty: Head Start Program. (Box 146, Folder 15)
  - Poverty: Health Care. (Box 146, Folder 16)
  - Poverty: History. (Box 146, Folder 17)
  - Poverty: Hunger. (Box 146, Folder 18)
  - Poverty: Income Guarantee. (Box 146, Folder 19)
  - Poverty: International. (Box 146, Folder 20)
  - Poverty: Ithaca. (Box 146, Folder 21)
  - Poverty: Jews. (Box 146, Folder 22)
  - Poverty: Justice. (Box 146, Folder 23)
  - Poverty: Justice. (Box 146, Folder 24)
  - Poverty: Justice. (Box 146, Folder 25)
  - Poverty: Justice. (Box 147, Folder 1)
  - Poverty: Law. (Box 147, Folder 2)
  - Poverty: Lawyers. (Box 147, Folder 3)
  - Poverty: Legal Aid to the Poor. (Box 147, Folder 4)
  - Poverty: Miscellaneous. (Box 147, Folder 5)
  - Poverty: Negro. (Box 147, Folder 6)
  - Poverty: New York State. (Box 147, Folder 7)
  - Poverty: 1971. (Box 147, Folder 8)
  - Poverty: 1973. (Box 147, Folder 9)
  - Poverty: Nixon Administration. (Box 147, Folder 10)
  - Poverty: Office of Economic Opportunity. (Box 147, Folder 11)
    "Opportunity" magazine published by the Office of Economic Opportunity.
  - Poverty: Participatory Democracy. (Box 147, Folder 12)
  - Poverty: Philosophy. (Box 147, Folder 13)
  - Poverty: Poor People's March on Washington, D.C. (Box 147, Folder 14)
  - Poverty: Religious Groups. (Box 147, Folder 15)
  - Poverty: Rural. (Box 147, Folder 16)
  - Poverty: Schools. (Box 147, Folder 17)
  - Poverty: Statistics. (Box 147, Folder 18)
  - Poverty: Third World. (Box 147, Folder 19)
  - Poverty: Unemployment. (Box 147, Folder 20)
  - Poverty: Unemployment. (Box 147, Folder 21)
  - Poverty: Universities. (Box 147, Folder 22)
  - Poverty: Urban. (Box 148, Folder 1)
  - Poverty: "War on Poverty." (Box 148, Folder 2)
  - Poverty: Women. (Box 148, Folder 3)
  - Poverty: "Working Poor." (Box 148, Folder 4)
  - Poverty: World. (Box 148, Folder 5)
  - Powell, Adam Clayton, Jr. (Box 148, Folder 6)
  - Power. (Box 148, Folder 7)
  - Pragmatism., 1960-1965 (Box 148, Folder 8)
    1965 reprint, "On the Unity of the Pragmatic Movement," signed by Charles Morris; 1960 reprint, "Pragmatism in America," signed by Sidney Ratner; article, no date, "Pragmatism, Pragmatism and the Will to Believe-- A Reconsideration," signed by Gail Kenned
  - Prayer., 1962 (Box 148, Folder 9)
    1962 reprint, "On Government and Prayer," signed by Edmond Cahn; 1962, "Statement on Proposed Amendments to the United States Constitution Concerning Prayers in Public Schools," submitted to the Senate Committee on the Judiciary by 132 Deans and Professor
  - Prayers., 1976 (Box 148, Folder 10)
  - Prayer: White House. (Box 148, Folder 11)
  - Precedent. (Box 148, Folder 12)
  - Presidency. (Box 148, Folder 13)
  - President. (Box 148, Folder 14)
  - Presidential Power. (Box 148, Folder 15)
  - President's Committee on Equal Employment Opportunity. (Box 148, Folder 16)
  - President's Committee on Government Contracts., 1957 (Box 148, Folder 17)
    Reprint, "The Nondiscrimination Clause in Government Contracts," signed by Robert S. Pasley.
  - Press. (Box 148, Folder 18)
  - Press. (Box 148, Folder 19)
  - Press. (Box 148, Folder 20)
  - Press. (Box 148, Folder 21)
  - Press. (Box 148, Folder 22)
  - Press. (Box 148, Folder 23)
  - Press. (Box 149, Folder 1)
  - Press, Access to., 1974 (Box 149, Folder 2)
    Memo, to: American Civil Liberties Union Board of Directors, from: Communications and Media Committee, re: Proposed policy statement on access to the media.
  - Press: Contempt. (Box 149, Folder 3)
  - Press Councils. (Box 149, Folder 4)
  - Press: Distribution. (Box 149, Folder 5)
  - Press, Freedom of., 1971 (Box 149, Folder 6)
    Memo, To: ACLU Board of Directors, From: the Office, re: Subpoena of newsmen issue; memo, no date, translation, memorandum on the freedom of information and of the press, prepared by the Alliance Israllite Universelle.
  - Press and Justice. (Box 149, Folder 7)
  - Press and Justice., 1971 (Box 149, Folder 8)
    Minutes, ACLU Board of Directors, 1966; minutes, ACLU Board of Directors
  - Press and Justice., 1976 (Box 149, Folder 9)
  - Press., 1953 (Box 149, Folder 10)
  - Press Permits. (Box 149, Folder 11)
  - Press Tax. (Box 149, Folder 12)
  - Preventive Detention. (Box 149, Folder 13)
  - Price Adjustments. (Box 149, Folder 14)
  - Price Fixing. (Box 149, Folder 15)
  - Princeton University. (Box 149, Folder 16)
  - Prisons. (Box 149, Folder 17)
  - Prisons. (Box 149, Folder 18)
  - Prisons. (Box 149, Folder 19)
  - Prisons. (Box 149, Folder 20)
  - Prisons. (Box 150, Folder 1)
  - Prisoners (Box 150, Folder 2)
  - Privacy. (Box 150, Folder 3)
  - Privacy, 1973 (Box 150, Folder 4)
    Report, American Civil Liberties Union Sexual Privacy Project Legal Docket.
  - Privacy. (Box 150, Folder 5)
  - Privacy, 1974 (Box 150, Folder 6)
    1974 memo, To: ACLU Board of Directors, From: Privacy Committee, re: Medical Records; 1974 report, ACLU Sexual Privacy Project Legal Docket.
  - Privacy, 1978 (Box 150, Folder 7)
    Memo, To: ACLU Board of Directors, From: Special Committee on Privacy, Libel and the Free Press, re: ACLU Policy on Privacy and Libel Law.
  - Privacy. (Box 150, Folder 8)
  - Privacy. (Box 151, Folder 1)
  - Privacy, 1965 (Box 151, Folder 2)
    Confidential report (for private circulation only) "Privacy in Western History: From the Age of Pericles to the American Republic" by Professor Alan F. Westin, Columbia University, 371 pages.
  - Privacy, 1964-1965 (Box 151, Folder 3)
    1964 report, for private circulation only, "Privacy and the Law" by William M. Beaney, Princeton University, 109 pages; 1965 confidential report, for private circulation only, "Privacy and Behavioral Research" by Oscar M. Ruebhausen and Orville G. Brim, J
  - Privacy. (Box 151, Folder 4)
  - Privacy. (Box 151, Folder 5)
  - Privacy. (Box 151, Folder 6)
  - Privacy. (Box 151, Folder 7)
  - Privacy, 1966 (Box 151, Folder 8)
    Letter, with attachment, signed by Senator Edward V. Long.
  - Privilege. (Box 151, Folder 9)
  - Privilege: Executive. (Box 152, Folder 1)
  - Privilege: General., 1973-1975 (Box 152, Folder 2)
    1975 memo, to: ACLU Board of Directors, from: Alan Reitman, re: Background material on professional privileges; 1975 memo, to: ACLU Board of Directors, From: Church-State Committee, re: Proposed policy on clergy-penitent privilege; 1973 memo, to: American
  - Privileges and Immunities. (Box 152, Folder 3)
  - Privilege: Newsman's., 1975 (Box 152, Folder 4)
    Memo, to: ACLU Board of Directors, from: Special Subcommittee formed to reconcile positions adopted by the Board on newsperson's privilege and researcher's privilege; report, no date, "American Bar Association Study Group on Journalists' Shield Legislatio
  - Privilege: Newspapers., 1976 (Box 152, Folder 5)
  - Probation. (Box 152, Folder 6)
  - Procedural. (Box 152, Folder 7)
  - Productivity. (Box 152, Folder 8)
  - Profanity. (Box 152, Folder 9)
  - Professional. (Box 152, Folder 10)
  - Professor. (Box 152, Folder 11)
  - Profit. (Box 152, Folder 12)
  - Profit Sharing., 1949 (Box 152, Folder 13)
    Report, "Profits Build a Financial Fortress: An Analysis of the Textile Industry's Ability to Weather Current Lull" by Textile Workers Union of America (TWUA), Research Department.
  - Programs and Lectures. (Box 152, Folder 14)
  - Progress. (Box 152, Folder 15)
  - Property. (Box 152, Folder 16)
  - Property: Acre Restrictions. (Box 152, Folder 17)
  - Property: Codes. (Box 152, Folder 18)
  - Property: Land Planning. (Box 152, Folder 19)
  - Protection of Foreign Born. (Box 152, Folder 20)
  - Protest: Cases. (Box 152, Folder 21)
  - Protestants and Others Newsletter., 1950 (Box 152, Folder 22)
    Newsletter, scattered issues, "Church and State Newsletter", by Protestants and Other Americans United for Separation of Church and State.
  - Psychedelics and Narcotics., 1967-1968 (Box 152, Folder 23)
    Minutes, Special Meeting of the American Civil Liberties Union Church-State Committee, 1967; 1968 memos, to: ACLU Board of Directors, from: Office, re: The equal protection argument and position paper on marijuana (ACLU working documents, not for public d
  - Psychoanalysis. (Box 152, Folder 24)
  - Psychology. (Box 152, Folder 25)
  - Psychiatry. (Box 152, Folder 26)
  - Psychopathic Personality. (Box 152, Folder 27)
  - Public Accommodations. (Box 152, Folder 28)
  - Public Defender. (Box 152, Folder 29)
  - Public Domain. (Box 153, Folder 1)
  - Public Education. (Box 153, Folder 2)
  - Public Employee. (Box 153, Folder 3)
  - Public Employee Relations. (Box 153, Folder 4)
  - Public Employment. (Box 153, Folder 5)
  - Public Employment Relations Board (PERB), New York State. (Box 153, Folder 6)
  - Public Interest Law. (Box 153, Folder 7)
  - Public Land. (Box 153, Folder 8)
  - Public Opinion. (Box 153, Folder 9)
  - Public Policy Digest. (Box 153, Folder 10)
  - Public Schools. (Box 153, Folder 11)
  - Public Sector Bargaining. (Box 153, Folder 12)
  - Public Travel. (Box 153, Folder 13)
  - Public Trial. (Box 153, Folder 14)
  - Public Utilities. (Box 153, Folder 15)
  - Publishers. (Box 153, Folder 16)
  - Puerto Rico. [folder 1 of 3], 1954-1965 (Box 153, Folder 17)
    Report, 2 volumes, "1965 Reports to the Middle States Association of Colleges and Universities;" "University of Puerto Rico, Program for the Future;" 1954 form letter, with attachments, from A. J. Muste regarding draft statement of Committee for Justice t
  - Puerto Rico. [folder 2 of 3], 1954-1965 (Box 153, Folder 18)
  - Puerto Rico. [folder 3 of 3], 1954-1965 (Box 153, Folder 19)
  - Punishment. (Box 153, Folder 20)
  - Punitive Damages. (Box 153, Folder 21)